Tastes like iron
When I'm in a pinch,
a hero is sure to appear
Tastes like iron
Know what, Smile?
（子供のペコ）
知ってるか？ スマイル
Blood tastes like iron.
血って鉄みたいな味するんだぜ
Not that one.
（男性）違うって おいちゃん
It's the red T-shirt over there.
そっちの赤いＴシャツだっての
No, no. On the other side.
違う違う　逆 逆
こっちだって こっち
Over here.
Tanaka, you forgot your shoes.
田中(たなか) シューズ忘れてんぞ
それ 中田(なかた)んだ
Those are Nakata's.
Final
ポカリと
ウーロンが３本
Three Pocaris and oolong teas.
Two Posts, VAAMs, and Gatorades.
I heard Kaiou lost
ポストとヴァームと
ゲータが２本に—
I heard Kaiou lost
It's 2 Katase guys
in the finals
I heard Kaiou lost
It's 2 Katase guys
in the finals
I heard Kaiou lost
It's 2 Katase guys
in the finals
I heard Kaiou lost
It's 2 Katase guys
in the finals
And one Aquarius.
それから
アクエリアスと…
（男性）書けよ
I heard Kaiou lost
It's 2 Katase guys
in the finals
Write it down.
I heard Kaiou lost
It's 2 Katase guys
in the finals
Wait, Dragon lost?
I heard Kaiou lost
It's 2 Katase guys
in the finals
The red one! How many times do I have to tell you?!
（男性）だから
赤いやつだっつうの
I'm leaving
Not gonna watch?
何回 言わすかね
I'm leaving
Not gonna watch?
Not interested
Who are we supposed to root for in this situation?
（高村(たかむら)）こういった場合
俺らは どっち応援するの？
（大田(おおた)）知らん
Beats me.
World Table Tennis
Kazama of Kaiou defeated in prelim semifinals
tabletennis
（ドラゴン）いえ
No, I wasn't injured.
Kanda Minoru
Winning streak ends!
故障などということは
ありません
Kanda Minoru
Winning streak ends!
Is Katase High that strong?!
Kanda Minoru
Winning streak ends!
Is Katase High that strong?!
Tsukimoto was the only one on my radar...
I was in top condition, and I feel that I played my best game.
体調は万全でしたし—
全力で戦えたと思います
I lost because I wasn't good enough.
自分の力が至らぬゆえの
敗北であり…
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
So hot...
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
暑(あち)い
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
He beat Kong
too, so he must
be the real deal
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Honestly, I don't
know!
That hitter was
awesome
Sakuma, what's with your hair?
（猫田(ねこた)）何や 佐久間(さくま) その頭
You're stylin'!
えらい いきっとんのう
（アクマ）ああ うっす
Heh, guess so.
Now that he's a free man, he wants to look his best.
（真田(さなだ)）そら 自由になったら
ツヤもつけよるやろ
You should drop by sometimes.
たまには顔ば出さんね
先生も心配しちょるき
Coach is worried about you.
Mr. Koizumi's boys sure are a surprise, huh?
（男性）しかし驚きましたね
小泉(こいずみ)さんところの２人
Tsukimoto's play resembles the way Butterfly Joe used to play.
（卓(たく)）月本(つきもと)君のプレーは—
往年のバタフライジョーを
ほうふつさせる
うちの大学 来るように
口利いてくれんか？ 風間(かざま)
Think you could talk him into
attending our university, Kazama?
I want the hitter.
俺は あの速攻 欲しいな
伸びるぜ ありゃ
That kid's got real potential!
（観客）
いつになったら始まんだよ
When is it gonna start?
Ten more minutes.
（観客）あと10分
Watching the final before you leave?
キャハハハハ ウッソ！
Waiting for it to start now
No way.
Watching the final before you leave?
Waiting for it to start now
Seriously?
Watching the final before you leave?
Waiting for it to start now
Will you be late?
マジかよ
Do you want coffee or tea?
Either's fine.
Pick one.
I'll have coffee, then.
（生徒）見てかねえの？ 決勝
You're not gonna watch the final?
（生徒）
関係ないっしょ 俺らには
It's got nothing to do with us.
Final
An all-Katase final...
（江上(えがみ)）片高(かたこう)同士の決勝？
海王(かいおう)でなく？
Not Kaiou?
Hoshino
Yutaka
(Katase
High)
Tsukimoto
Makoto
(Katase
High)
Tsuki...
月(つき)…
What?
あいつだ
It's him.
（男性）見ろよ 指！
Follow the finger!
Not yours, you idiot! My finger!
違うよ バカ！ 俺の指だよ！
Testing, testing.
（アナウンス）
あー テス テス
The odds would've been high
if you could've bet on it
あー マイクテスト
マイクテスト
Mic test, mic test.
The odds would've been high
if you could've bet on it
It's exciting when
they're both nobodies
The odds would've been high
if you could've bet on it
あー あー テス テス
Testing, testing...
Winning streak ends!
Youth Olympics Gold Medalist
海王じゃねえの 片高
片瀬(かたせ)高校よ
It's not Kaiou. It's Katase High. Katase High School!
Kazama lost. No, seriously.
負けちゃったのよ 風間君
いや マジで
Time for the final
Not interested
Grab something to eat when it's over?
Pasta?
Cold noodles
（浜(はま)ちょん）あっ
（小泉）ハロー キャプテン大田
Hello, Captain Oota.
ミスター星野(ほしの)は？
Where's Mr. Hoshino?
He's not here yet.
まだみたいっす
His knee must be in bad shape.
（小泉）
かなり悪いのかね？ 膝の具合
I haven't heard anything.
（大田）
さあ 今は俺 聞いてねえっす
Hey, Coach, who are we supposed to root for in this situation?
（高村）ねえ先生 こういう場合
俺ら どっち応援すんの？
Both of them, Mr. Takamura.
（小泉）
どちらもさ ミスター高村
You cheer whenever either scores a point.
どちらのポイントにも
声援で応えればいいよ
Mr. Tsukimoto.
ミスター月本
君なら打てたかね？
Could you have done it?
Driven a stake into an old friend's injury?
旧友の傷に
くぎを突き立てるような球を
選手生命を奪う危険なコースにさ
Used a strategy that might end his career?
Could you have done it?
君なら打てたか？
I can do it.
（スマイル）
僕は打てますよ 先生
Against an opponent with a weak right knee,
右膝が弱い相手なら—
I'll hit deep to the forehand,
then switch to his backhand side.
フォアに深く打って
バックに切り返します
Wait, you're going after Hoshino's knee?
（高村）え？ それ星野の膝
攻めるってこと？
What's wrong with you?
何 言ってんだよ てめえ
Question for you, Mr. Tsukimoto.
ミスター月本にクエスチョン
What happens when someone
goes after a hero's weak point?
弱点を攻められたヒーローは
どうなるね？
Heroes don't have weak points.
（スマイル）
ヒーローに弱点などありません
Okay, Mr. Tsukimoto.
オーケー ミスター月本
You really are the greatest player in my eyes.
やはり君は 私の知るかぎり
最も素晴らしい選手だよ
６番コート 決勝戦
On court six, the final match!
Hoshino of Katase High vs.
Tsukimoto, also of Katase High!
片瀬高校 星野選手
同校 月本選手
What's wrong, Captain? Hoshino's a no-show.
どうした キャプテン
星野 いないじゃん
Math Test
Hoshino "Third Child" Yutaka
Shinjiiiii!
AT field
I mustn't run!
Hey, did you see Hoshino's paper?
（子供）
おいおい あれ見た？
星野の答案
（子供）
見た 見た ０点！
バカ丸出しな
Yeah—zero points! I can't believe how dumb he is!
今日も休むとさ 例のあれでよ
He said he'd be out today. You know, for the usual.
Good. The classroom will be nice and peaceful.
そいつはよかった
教室 平和で
Hey, Golgo! Go buy me some coffee milk!
おい ゴルゴ！
俺様にコーヒー牛乳 買ってこい
ダッシュな
And make it snappy.
欲しければ
自分で買いに行くといいよ
If you want some, go buy it yourself.
ええ？ 何だ てめえ
Whoa, you think you can talk like that when Hoshino ain't here?
星野いないのに
その口の利き方
Robots can't disobey humans!
ロボットは
人間に逆らえないんだぞ
Don't you know the three laws of robotics?
ロボット３原則
知らねえのかよ
Get going, or I'll lock you up again!
さっさと行けよ
また監禁すっぞ 監禁
Cut it out. We've got trouble! Hoshino's here!
（子供）よせ よせ ヤバいよ
いるって星野
Ahem! Thank you very much!
（子供のペコ）アー ウェー
サンキュー ベルマッチョ！
Ulp!
（子供）ゲロゲロ
（子供）待てよ おい 俺は…
Wait! I didn't—
（子供）ギャー！
（子供）やめてー！
Stop!
If you're pissed off, get mad. If something's funny, laugh.
頭にきたら怒りゃあいいし
おかしきゃ笑えよ
お前 見てんと—
I get annoyed watching you sometimes.
何か時々
イラついてくんよ
（子供のスマイル）
うん 分かった　努力してみる
Okay. I'll try.
Dang, you're weird.
（子供のペコ）
けっ 変わってやがんな
訳分かんねえよ
I don't get you at all.
どうして星野は
いつも学校サボるの？
Why do you always skip school?
Do you hate school?
学校 嫌い？
You haven't heard?
聞いてねえか？ 試合さ 卓球の
I've got table tennis matches.
Table tennis?
卓球？
Open up my bag.
俺のランドセル 開けてみそ
（子供のペコ）
今日は横浜　来週は千葉
Yokohama today, and Chiba next week.
出られる大会 全部行く
I enter all the tournaments I can.
（子供のスマイル）強いんだ
So you're good?
I'm unbeatable!
無敵だよ
Wow.
キャハッ 俺への挑戦
３世紀 早まったな アクマ
You need another 300 years of
practice to challenge me, Demon!
（子供のアクマ）
ちっ うるせえよ
Shut up.
C'mere, Tsukimoto.
（子供のペコ）来い 月本
（子供のスマイル）え？
Huh?
Come here and play with us.
こっち来て一緒にやるべえよ
僕は いいよ
見てるだけで面白いから
I'll pass.
I'm having fun just watching.
Ugh, isn't he the nerd from Class 3?
（子供のアクマ）けっ こいつ
３組のガリ勉じゃねえか
What's he doing here?
なんで こんな所にいるんだよ
（子供のペコ）
見て分かるもんじゃ
ねえのよ これは
You can't learn this just from watching.
It's not like a math test.
算数テストとは
ちと違う
（子供のスマイル）でも…
But...
I'll teach ya!
おいらが教えてやんよ
Okay.
Viva!
（ペコ）ビバ！
You're late, Peco.
遅いよ ペコ
ヘヘッ そう言ってくれるな
Aw, don't say that.
これでも すっ飛ばしてきたんよ
I got here as fast as I could.
Yeah.
（ペコ）いくぜ 相棒
（スマイル）うん
Let's do this, partner!
Yeah.
Hoshino Yutaka
Tsukimoto
Makoto
A new age has dawned, and still I can't make a decision
My path is too straight for my taste, but I'll walk it
I can't choose just yet
I have to think about it
I have no idea what I want to do
I'm going crazy!
Comparing yourself to others just makes you depressed
I'm alone in this world
I'm always alone here
Still I'm gonna do it
Maybe there's nothing that only I can do
But there's no way that I
But there's no way that I won't try to leave my mark
I just want to have my fun, whatever the times
Tastes like iron
My blood tastes like iron
When I'm in a pinch,
a hero is sure to appear
He's sure to appear
My blood tastes like iron
Blood Tastes Like Iron
Deep to the forehand, then switch to his backhand side...
（スマイルの声）
フォアに深く打って
バックに切り返せば…
The hero is sure to appear
He's sure to appear!
（スマイルの声）
血は鉄の味がする
Blood tastes like iron.
Never close your fingers around the ball.
球のせる手は
握ったらダメだ
Hold it above the table.
ほいで コートより
高く構えんよ
Make it bounce once on your side first.
１回 こっち
ワンバンさせんさ
Got it, Tsukimoto?
分かんか？ 月本
Yeah.
Now give it a shot!
ほいじゃ やってみそ
Okay.
（子供のスマイル）分かった
やってみる
I'll try it!
It 's safe and quiet here.
（子供のスマイルの声）
ここは静かで安全だ
とても落ち着く
I really feel at ease.
I 'm quiet like a robot.
ロボットみたいに静かにしてる
Someone 's coming!
（子供のスマイルの声）誰か来る
大丈夫
僕はここで平気なんだ
It 's okay.
I 'm fine here.
Nothing will happen to me while I 'm in here.
ここにいれば何もされない
Robot
Box
Where's your
battery?
switch?
Walking
Robot
Cleaning
怒らないし 笑わない
I don 't yell and I don 't laugh.
I don 't even breathe.
息もしない　ただいるだけ
I 'm just here.
外へ出たら また…
If I go out there, it 'll happen again...
また…
（子供のペコ）
違うぜ スマイル
You're wrong, Smile.
It tastes like iron
Know what, Smile?
知ってるか？ スマイル
血って
鉄の味がするんだぜ
Blood tastes like iron!
Say what?
（子供のスマイル）何？ それ
全然 分かんないよ
I don't get it.
Let's play table tennis, Smile!
（子供のペコ）
卓球しようぜ スマイル
Table tennis, table tennis, table tennis!
卓球 卓球 卓球！
I'll teach ya!
俺が教えてやんよ！
That's great. You're good!
ほら いいぞ　うまい！
力いっぱい打て！
Hit it as hard as you can!
ほら 見れ　おもしろ～！
Check this out. It's neat!
俺らの中 こんななってんさ
This is what we look like on the inside.
Even a small cut
Is a flood on the inside
Better stop it soon or
there will be trouble!
Stopped!
We're platelets!
ほら 見ぃ
Look.
手の中の血が透けて赤く見えんよ
It looks red because the blood's showing through your hands.
Try it, Smile. Give it a go.
スマイルもやってみ
やってみそ
See? There's blood flowing in you too.
ほら スマイルの中にも
血が流れとん
Bright red blood.
真っ赤な血が
Put some spirit into it, Smile!
気合 入れろ スマイル！
Men are all about guts!
男は ど根性だかんよ！
Blow him away!
吹っ飛ばせ！
スマイル！
Smile!
いくぞー！ スマイル
Here we go, Smile!
えい
Yeah!
っしゃー！
（ペコ）ウハハハッ
３世紀 早まったね スマイル！
You need another 300 years, Smile!
ハァ ハァ ハァ…
My blood tastes like iron.
（スマイルの声）
僕の血は鉄の味がする
Blood tastes like
iron
僕の血は鉄の味がする
My blood tastes like iron.
Blood
tastes
like
iron
Looks like his knee is okay...
Yeah.
やつをノーマークにしちょったんは
迂闊(うかつ)やったのう
We were careless not to keep an eye on him.
It wouldn't have changed anything if we had.
マークしたところで
結果は同じだよ
（オババ）あの子が
精いっぱいの力で遊べんのは—
Peco's the only one that boy can play all-out with.
ペコだけなんだよ
Think Peco is okay?
（道夫(みちお)）大丈夫かな ペコ
Knee's probably killing him.
しんどいだろうねえ
風間の時も母ちゃん止めた？
Mom—did you try to stop Kazama back then?
アッハハハ
Just wondering, that's all!
一度
聞いてみたかっただけなんだ
You don't have to answer.
答えなくていいよ
ハハハハハハ
The hero transcends logic.
（スマイルの声）
ヒーローは理屈を超えてゆく
The hero overturns what we though we knew, and drives away the darkness.
ヒーローは常識を覆し—
闇を吹っ飛ばす
More than anything, he shines simply, brightly, and happily.
何より単純で—
明るく 楽しく 輝いている
Yeah!
っしゃー！
（江上の声）まいったな
I 'll be dammed.
I actually like table tennis.
俺 卓球 好きじゃんよ
お前から離れて
あちこち巡ってきたけんど—
I left you and wandered the world,
but I was looking for you this whole time.
俺 ずっとお前を捜してた
I 'm sorry.
ごめんな　許してくれっか
Will you forgive me?
Will you let me start over?
もっかい
一から やらしてくれっか？
I swear I 'll never let you go again!
今度こそ お前を離さねえかんよ
ハァ…
What's wrong, Tamura?
（小泉）どうした 田村(たむら)
トイレじゃなかったのか？
I thought you were in the bathroom.
立ち続けんのも こたえる年さね
Standing too long takes a toll at my age.
And it's not like it matters who wins this one.
勝ち負けが意味持つ
試合でもねえしな
Make sure you take Hoshino
to the hospital once it's over.
試合が終わったら
星野 病院 連れてけよ
I'm sure he's barely on his feet.
立っとるだけで必死のはずだ
Yeah.
I know.
分かってる
Yeah.
Hey.
（風間理事長）いやあ
Long time no see.
久しぶり
It's Poseidon's CEO.
ポセイドンのＣＥＯだ
ずいぶんな商売
するじゃねえか
You do brutal business.
Can't believe you put out mats for high schoolers.
高校生にも
マット敷かせようなんて
You know, I thought winning would make everyone happy,
勝つことが みんなを幸せにすると
思ってたんだがなあ
but Ryuuichi says he's leaving home, not to mention my son and granddaughter...
竜一(りゅういち)は家を出ると言って
息子と孫も…
You've gained weight.
お前 太ったな
お前 誰のために卓球やってる？
Who do you play table tennis for?
無論 みんなのため
For all of us, of course.
Pull the other one.
ウソつけ
まっ あんたらしい答えだけどな
That's very you, though.
（小泉）お前 俺に根性で勝ったと
言い触らしてるらしいじゃないか
I hear you've been telling people you beat me through sheer grit.
After I let you win.
俺が負けてやったのにさ
Drop that, okay?
もう それは言うな
I was really torn up about it afterward.
その件は ずいぶん
あとから悩んだ
Let's play table tennis.
卓球しようぜ
What?
私を見んな
巻き込むんじゃねえよ
Don't look at me; I'm staying out of it.
膝が悪いんだからさ
I've got a bad knee, you know.
（風間理事長）動かなくていいよ
You won't have to move!
I've got a great racket for senior citizens.
今 シニア用のいいラケット
あるんだよ
What?
Sheesh, you're a shrewd salesman!
（小泉）
商魂たくましいな まったく
Can I be like you?
（子供のスマイル）なれるかな
Think I can be like you, Peco?
僕もペコみたいになれるかな？
We are all alive
We are alive, and that's why we sing
We're alive, and that's why we get sad
If I hold my palm up to the sun and look,
I can see my warm, red blood flowing
Even worms and crickets and water bugs
are all alive like us
They're our friends
We are all alive
We're alive, and that's why we laugh
We're alive, and that's why we feel joy
スマイル 勝手にやらすなよ
きちっとコーチしな
Smile! Don't just turn them loose! Actually coach them!
Okay.
Gather 'round, everybody.
エブリバディ 集合
（子供たち）オーエッ！
Yes, Coach!
今日は君らに
かっちょいい魔球を授けるぜ
Today, I shall teach you a sweet unhittable serve!
Yay!
（子供たち）うわーい！
（オババ）真面目にやれよ
Be serious.
（ドラゴン）おす
Hey.
It's Kazama, live in person!
風間選手だ　本物！
You'll get pollen on you.
花粉が付くよ
You're so cool, Kazama.
かっちブーだな 風間にいちゃん
（ドラゴン）
ちびども 元気にしとったか？
Have you been well, kids?
（子供）じでだー！
（子供）ギャングみてえ！
Yeah.
You're dressed like a gangster!
It's good to see you again, Tamura.
ご無沙汰してます 田村さん
I brought you some flowers.
花 持ってきたんですが
Now that 's unusual.
（オババ）
珍しいね　花瓶なんかあったかね
Not sure I even have a vase.
Do you have some time, Tsukimoto?
少し時間あるか？ 月本
ねえよ
No.
Sure.
いいですよ
おい！
Hey!
（オババ）
ちっ ろくなコーチしねえわ
おまけにバックレるわ
Hmph! He hardly coaches, and he skips on top of that...
誰に似たんだか まったく
I have no idea who he takes after.
（オババ）
オラ！ 声出せ ガキども！
Let me hear you, brats!
（子供たち）オーエッ！
Yes, Coach!
Looking for something?
（小泉夫人）捜し物？
鍋… どこ？
The hot pot.
Where is it?
Honey, it's June!
６月よ 今
今日は誠(まこと)が来る
Makoto's coming today.
Yes, but not until dinner!
（小泉夫人）
来るって 晩ごはんでしょ？
まだ お昼過ぎよ
It's only a bit past noon now!
Pot, pot. Where are you?
（小泉）鍋 鍋 どこよ
I see. You're an elementary school teacher.
（ドラゴン）そうか
月本は小学校の先生か
来週から実習です
I start student teaching next week.
しかし惜しいなあ
I have to say, it's a shame.
君なら
優れた選手にもなれただろうに
You could've become an excellent player.
You're the only one who says that anymore.
今じゃ そんなこと言ってくれるの
風間さんぐらいです
It feels kind of nice.
何か悪い気しないですね
（ドラゴン）クソ！
Damn it.
They cut me from the Olympic team.
私はね
世界代表から外されてしまったよ
（スマイル）知ってます
I know...
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Kong's been doing well.
コンも調子がいいですからね
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
Five Years after Naturalization, Finally a Ticket to the
Olympics for Tsujidou Wenge (Chinese Name Kong Wenge)
Kazama Cut From Team
I used to hate my father so much, but I'm becoming like him lately.
（ドラゴン）親父(おやじ)が嫌いで
しょうがなかったが—
最近 親父に似てきたよ
Sometimes I worry...
時々 考えるんだ
自分は このまま—
Maybe I'll end up just a mediocre player from now on.
凡庸な選手で
終わってしまうのではないかと
いいじゃないですか　凡庸
What's wrong with being mediocre?
僕 わりと好きですよ
そういう選手
I like players like that, personally.
（ドラゴン）
バカ言うな イヤだよ
Don't be stupid. I'm not okay with it!
We'll now begin the fifth match!
（ドイツ語の
アナウンス）
おい ペコ！
出番だ 急げ！
Hey Peco, you're up! Get a move on!
Number five, representing Japan...
（ペコ）
おっと ヤベえ ヤベえ
Whoops, better hurry.
（ドイツ語の
アナウンス）
The Japanese ace aiming for the top in a sport
where China dominates the world rankings!
（歓声）
（ペコ）ういーっす
Hey.
Danke, danke.
ダンケ ダンケ
（ペコ）愛してんよ
I love ya.
Did you hear? Demon's gonna have a kid.
（スマイル）知ってます？
アクマ 子供が生まれるの
His third?
（ドラゴン）３人目か
Yeah. He said he was going to buy a truck and set out on his own.
（スマイル）ええ
今度 トラック買って独立するって
しばらく道場も来れないって
言ってましたよ
He said he wouldn't be able to stop by the hall for a while.
I see.
（ドラゴン）そっか
ああ！ クソ！
Damn it!
He was fired up to earn money.
（スマイル）
稼ぐ気 満々でしたよ
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
And the woman from the Poseidon
commercials was in the news, wasn't she?
ポセイドンのＣＭの人も
記事 出てましたね
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
Japanese Designer Working in Paris
Popular Brand Designer
Kazama Yurie
You know a lot.
（ドラゴン）詳しいな
Everything's on the web these days.
（スマイル）
何でもウェブに出てますからね
You look things up?
お前が検索したりするのか？
I do.
（スマイル）しますよ
Damn it!
（ドラゴン）クソ！
Do you have a girlfriend?
お前 彼女いるのか？
Wouldn't you like to know.
（スマイル）さあ どうでしょう
So you do?!
（ドラゴン）いるのか！
Did I go wrong somewhere, maybe?
俺は どっかで間違えたのかなあ
I don't think devoting your life to table tennis is such a bad thing, really.
本当は 卓球に懸ける人生も
悪くないと思います
No way in hell do I want that.
イヤだよ そんなの絶対
（スマイル）来ますね 夏
Summer is coming...
（ドラゴン）そうだな
Yeah.
（スマイル）
また にぎやかになりますね
Things will get lively again.
Yeah.
I'm sleepy.
眠いや
Fin
A red sun stares at me
The world goes blurry when I yawn
My wishes fluctuate like a metronome
Everything tells me this is the end
I do have some dreams, you know
Sometimes we breathe
and just seem to inhale the smoke of someone
somewhere out of sight
Then we are pure determination
I don't understand this wonderland
I won't get wet even if it rains
This is a wonderland
Once I've made it through this long tunnel
I'm sure that someone will kiss me